[{"answer": " Im so excited that were going to go on vacation together next year", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Me too!  When should we go", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Im so excited that were going to go on vacation together next year", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " I think the summer time would be good, dont you", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Me too!  When should we go", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Yeah, I think so.  Its always easier to take time off from work during the summer", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 15, "question": " I think the summer time would be good, dont you", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " I cant wait", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Yeah, I think so.  Its always easier to take time off from work during the summer", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " So, where should we go?  Do you want to go somewhere tropical", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 17, "question": " I cant wait", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " I do love going to the beach.  We could lie in the sun, go swimming, go surfing", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 18, "question": " So, where should we go?  Do you want to go somewhere tropical", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " That would be very relaxing", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 22, "question": " I do love going to the beach.  We could lie in the sun, go swimming, go surfing", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " But wait, didnt you go to the beach last year for your vacation", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 23, "question": " That would be very relaxing", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Yeah, I went to Mexico.  It was gorgeous", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 24, "question": " But wait, didnt you go to the beach last year for your vacation", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Well, since you did that last year, why dont we pick a different kind of place", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Yeah, I went to Mexico.  It was gorgeous", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Sure, that sounds good", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Well, since you did that last year, why dont we pick a different kind of place", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " How about Canada?  Maybe Vancouver", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Sure, that sounds good", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " No, its too cold and rainy in that city", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 31, "question": " How about Canada?  Maybe Vancouver", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " All right.  How about New York City?  That would be exciting", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 32, "question": " No, its too cold and rainy in that city", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " No, I was kind of hoping to go somewhere outside of the U.S", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 33, "question": " All right.  How about New York City?  That would be exciting", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " OK.  How about Europe", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 34, "question": " No, I was kind of hoping to go somewhere outside of the U.S", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " That sounds perfect!  Europe", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 35, "question": " OK.  How about Europe", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Any ideas on where you might want to go", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 36, "question": " That sounds perfect!  Europe", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Ive heard of a great town called Toulouse in France.  Its supposed to be ver", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Any ideas on where you might want to go", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " I dont know about that.  It sounds like that city is too small.  Dont you think we", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Ive heard of a great town called Toulouse in France.  Its supposed to be ver", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Yeah, I guess there wouldnt be that much to do there", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 45, "question": " I dont know about that.  It sounds like that city is too small.  Dont you think we", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " How about London?  There is a ton to do there", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Yeah, I guess there wouldnt be that much to do there", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " I think London would be too big of a city.  There are so many people and it woul", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 47, "question": " How about London?  There is a ton to do there", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " But it would be so exciting.  We could figure out how to get around, dont yo", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 51, "question": " I think London would be too big of a city.  There are so many people and it woul", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " I know, I know.  I just dont like huge cities.  You know me; Im a country girl", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 55, "question": " But it would be so exciting.  We could figure out how to get around, dont yo", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Well, there must be someplace we can compromise on", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 56, "question": " I know, I know.  I just dont like huge cities.  You know me; Im a country girl", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": "Hmmmm.  Lets think", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Well, there must be someplace we can compromise on", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Ive got it", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Hmmmm.  Lets think", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " What", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Ive got it", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " How about Florence, Italy or Dublin, Ireland?  Both are medium sized cities tha", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 63, "question": " What", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " A medium sized city sounds perfect", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 67, "question": " How about Florence, Italy or Dublin, Ireland?  Both are medium sized cities tha", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Which do you prefer?  Florence or Dublin", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 68, "question": " A medium sized city sounds perfect", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Well, between the two, Id pick Dublin", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Which do you prefer?  Florence or Dublin", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Because you want to go to the Guinness factory", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Well, between the two, Id pick Dublin", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " No, because they speak English there", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Because you want to go to the Guinness factory", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Oh, OK.  I guess that would make things easier for us", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 72, "question": " No, because they speak English there", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Is that OK with you", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Oh, OK.  I guess that would make things easier for us", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Sure.  Dublin it is.  I cant wait to start planning our trip there", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Is that OK with you", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Me too", "docId": "09-03", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Sure.  Dublin it is.  I cant wait to start planning our trip there", "qSentId": 74}]
